http://spiderlink.com/privacy-notice/

(310)379-6429
24/7x365 Support:
Privacy Notice
Personal Information:
Spiderlink.com is committed to protecting your privacy. We do not sell, rent, or lease our customer lists or information to third parties. All billing information you provide including email addressses are kept in the strictest of confidence.
Use of your Personal Information:
Spiderlink.com collects and uses your personal information to operate and improve its site and deliver the services you have requested. These uses may include providing you with more effective customer service; making the sites or services easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information; performing research and analysis aimed at improving our products, services and technologies.
We also use your personal information to communicate with you. We may send certain mandatory service communications such as welcome notices, information on technical service issues, billings statements, and promotional announcements. We may also occasionally send you product surveys or promotional mailings to inform you of other products or services available from Spiderlink.com
Accessing your Personal Information:
Spiderlink Clients have the ability to view or edit their personal information online. In order to help prevent your personal information from being viewed by others, you will be required to sign in with your login information (userid and password). The Client Login page allows you to update your email address and any Billing information, as well as opt in or opt out of our mailing list.
Terms of Use | Privacy Notice | Billing Policy
All Rights Reserved - Copyright © 2013 Spiderlink Web Services, Inc.
All trademarks are the property of their respective owners.
